http://www.docosoft.com/fns/privacy

DOCOsoft - Claims Management and Document Management Solutions
HomeAbout Us
Who We AreWhat We DoWhy DOCOsoftContact DetailsRequest for InformationCareers
Workflow Solutions
Solvency II WorkflowsBespoke WorkflowsBusiness Process Management Workflow Technology
Document Management Solutions
DOCO Treasury Enterprise DMSDOCO desknet SBEDOCO soloDOCO WebArchive
SharePoint Solutions
Outlook pluginEmbedded ViewerScanning SolutionCustom Workflow
Technical Services
ConsultingProject ManagementCustomisationDevelopmentIntegration
White Papers
Claims ManagementDocument ManagementScanning SolutionsSharePoint SolutionsDrawing Management
PostersBrochuresVideos
News & Events
Latest NewsNews ArchiveEventsEvent ArchivePress ReleasesPress ArchiveNewslettersBlogThought Leadership
Privacy Policy
We respect the rights of our users and do not, as a general rule, collect personal information of any kind. Any personal information that you volunteer (for example by registering for an eMail subscription service) will be treated with the highest standards of security and confidentiality, strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Act, 1988, as amended by the Data Protection (Amendment) Act, 2003. Any information that you provide in this way is used only in line with the purpose for which you provided it. Where a user voluntarily provides personal information in response to a questionnaire or survey the data will be used for research or analysis purposes only. For general web browsing no personal information is revealed to us, although certain statistical information is available to us via our internet service provider. This information may include
The logical address of the server you are using The top level domain name from which you access the Internet (for example, .ie, com, .org etc.) The type of browser you are using. The date and time you access our site The Internet address used to link to our site
Some of the above information is used to create summary statistics which allow us to assess the number of visitors to our site, identify what pages are accessed most frequently and generally, help us to make our site more user-friendly Usage of Google Analytics This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Back to top
Our Clients Client List
Success Stories
Client Support & Services
Our Solutions Claims Management Solutions
Document Management Solutions
Drawing Management Solutions
Useful Links Contact Details Careers Support Details Remote Support
Contact Us
Follow us:
FacebookTwitter LinkedIn
